准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
油漆工
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
蟹堡王
蟹堡王生意清淡的一天
A slow day at the Krusty Krab
章鱼哥  快看看这个
Hey, Squidward, check this out
两块普通的蟹黄堡肉饼
Two ordinary Krabby Patties
但是一旦技艺精湛地投出去
but when expertly tossed with the skill of a champ
就会变成
they become
通向痛苦的单程票
A one-way ticket to pain
起锚
Heave ho
这外面到底怎么一回事
What the devilfish is going on out here?
时间就是金钱
Time is money
要是你们在浪费时间
and if you boys is wasting time
那就是在浪费金钱
then you're wasting money
那样恶心得很
And that's just sick
可是我们是在做招徕顾客的仪式啊
But we were performing a ritual to attract customers
真要想引到顾客  必须要让咱伤着
and the only way it can work is for us to get hurt
伤势要很重
real bad
哪个傻子跟你们说要那样的
What stupid barnacle told you that?
听好  你们别自残了
Listen, instead of killing yourselves
我有非常重要的事情要交给你们
I've got something real important for you to do for me
你们有没有准备好面对你们的超级
Now, are you men ready for your super
超级
"Super"
特别
Special
"Special"
神秘
Secret
"Secret"
的任务
Assignment
别吊我们胃口了
Put us out of our misery
一定要知道  一定要知道
I gotta know, I gotta know
你们两个要帮我粉刷房子内墙
The two of you are to paint the inside of me house
但我得先警告你们两个
But, let me give you two a warning
这油漆是永久性的
This here paint is absolutely permanent
永远都不会脱落
It will never come off
要是让我看到油漆滴到墙以外的东西
so if I see even one drop on anything but wall
我就割掉你们屁股  挂到我壁炉上面
I'll have your rear ends cut off
and mounted over me fireplace
海绵宝宝
派大星
祝你们干活愉快
So have fun with the job
派大星
Patrick
怎么了  海绵宝宝
Yeah, SpongeBob
蟹老板的珍贵宝物好多啊
Mr. Krabs sure has a lot of expensive treasures
个个都容易滴上油漆
to drip paint on
你说该不该把墙上的东西拿下来
Do you think we should take this stuff off the walls?
不该  海绵宝宝
No way, SpongeBob
搬东西又不会加工钱
We're not getting paid to move stuff
派大星  我们根本就领不到工钱
Patrick, we're not getting paid at all
我说的就这个意思
Well, that's what I said
我们不领工钱  就这么定了
We're not getting paid, and that's final
好吧  那就绕开这些东西刷
Okay, we'll just paint around all this stuff
不错  别给我工钱就行
Good, just don't pay me
我们首先要铺防水布
First, we need to set out the tarp
防水布来了
Tarp, ahoy
咱还得要再铺些  派大星
We're going to need more coverage, Patrick
现在这样才像话
Now, that's what I'm talking about
我们应该得打开这几罐
Well, I guess we should open these cans of
永久性油漆了
permanent paint now
这种油漆永远都不脱落
That will never, ever come off
要是沾上什么别的东西
And if we get it on anything
蟹老板就会割掉我们的屁股
Mr. Krabs will cut our butts off
然后挂到墙壁上
And mount them on the wall
小心点  海绵宝宝
Careful, SpongeBob
海绵宝宝  小心点
SpongeBob, careful
小心点  海绵宝宝
Careful, SpongeBob
派大星  盖子已经开完了
Patrick, the lid's already off
现在轮我了
Now it' my turn
这罐也让我来开吧  派大星
I should do this one, too, Patrick
真是劣质
Well, that was a rip-off
派大星  准备好刷子吧
Okay, Patrick, let's get our brushes ready
还是先用小一点的刷子好
Maybe we should start with a smaller brush
派大星  得开始
All right, Patrick, got to get started
刷这面墙了
painting this wall
要用永久性油漆  不能滴到别的东西
with the permanent paint that we can't get on anything
只能刷墙
but the wall
那就  开始刷了
Well, here we go
一小时后
再让我做会心理准备
Just a few more seconds of mental preparation
我就可以开始刷墙了
and I'll be painting this wall
两小时后
我就要开始刷了
I'm getting to the painting
三小时后
就不能快点吗
Can you move it along?
我转场都用光了
I'm all out of time cards
没问题
No problem
我刷了
Here I go
好
Yeah
真见鬼
Barnacles
还会有比大油漆泡泡更糟的东西吗
What could be worse than a giant paint bubble?
这我知道
I know
两个大油漆泡泡
Two giant paint bubbles
派大星
Patrick
咋了  海绵宝宝
Yeah, SpongeBob
这泡泡不能再大下去了
I don't think this bubble can get much bigger
胡扯
Nonsense
派大星  不要
Pat, no
成功了
We did it
整间房都刷完了
We painted the whole house
而且油漆一滴都没沾到墙以外的东
and without getting a drop of paint on anything but the
怎么会这样
Flopping flotsam
那是个什么鬼
What's that?
我们完蛋了  派大星
We're dead, Patrick
知道那什么东西吗
Do you know what that is?
是一块钱
It's a dollar
我赢了
I win
那不单单是一块钱
That's not just a dollar
是蟹老板赚到的第一块钱
It's Mr. Krabs's first dollar
他最珍贵的宝物
his most prized possession
我们把油漆沾到上面去了
And we got paint on it
你太过激了  海绵宝宝
I think you are overreacting, SpongeBob
我没看到有油漆啊
I don't see any paint
问题不大
Okay, this isn't a problem
也许擦掉就行
Maybe I can just wipe it off
好了  应该行了
There, I think I got it
这下看到油漆了
Now I see it
这可不好  派大星
This is not good, Patrick
这可不好
This is not good
蟹老板马上就要回来了
Mr. Krabs is going to be home soon
一旦他看到我们把他第一块钱怎么了
and when he sees what we did to his dollar
海绵宝宝
派大星
等等  海绵宝宝
Wait, SpongeBob
只要把油漆洗掉
all we got to do is wash the paint off
蟹老板就不会知道了
and Krabs will never know
可是蟹老板说过
But Mr. Krabs said
管他蟹老板说的什么鬼话
Forget what Mr. Krabs said
肯定有东西能让油漆脱落
Every paint comes off with something
脱落了吗
Did it work?
没
No
脱落了吗
Did it work?
没
No
脱落了吗
Did it work?
没
No
啥都脱不掉
Nothing's working
等下  海绵宝宝
Wait, SpongeBob
我们可不是原始人
We're not cavemen
我们拥有高科技
We have technology
没脱落
It didn't work
都要怪蟹老板
This is all Mr. Krabs' fault
要是他一开始没把那臭钱挂那里
If he hadn't hung that stupid dollar in the first place
这钱明明跟普普通通的一块钱没两样
I mean, it's not like it looks any different
than a regular dollar
干嘛要挂
Why hang it?
随便搞个什么旧钱搁墙上不就行了
You could just stick any old dollar bill up on the wall
根本就看不出来哪有区别
No one would even know the difference
你倒也可以掏我钱包
You might as well just reach into my wallet
拿出来一块钱  再挂到墙上去
pull out a dollar and put it on the wall
快点  派大星
Hurry, Patrick
钱包拿出来
take out your wallet
不知道你要拿这干嘛
I don't see where you're going with this
一块钱
A dollar
我们屁股保住了  派大星
Our butts are saved, Patrick
现在我们得要
Now all we have to
派大星  不要
Patrick, no
糖果
派大星  不要
Patrick, no
投币
你投什么投
Why did you put it?
快取  派大星
Grab it, Pat
取出来
grab it
赶紧  赶紧
Hurry, hurry
派大星  别啊
Pat, no, no
拿  派大星
Get it, Pat
拿啊拿啊拿啊
get it, get it, get it
要来一口吗
Want a bite?
没事  还有时间
Okay, okay, we still got time
不要恐惧  海绵宝宝
Don't panic, SpongeBob
恐惧就是敌人
panic is the enemy
你很强大
You are strong
你可以用你的力量克服的
Through your strength you shall overcome
自己看着办吧  好哥们
You're on your own, pal
赶紧  派大星
Hurry, Patrick
把蟹老板的钱挂回墙上去
put the dollar back on the wall
我有办法了
I got an idea
什么
What the?
完工了  老板
We're all done, sir
可好看了
Everything looks great
对啊  你看都没必要看
Yeah, you don't have to look around
我们已经帮你看完了
We already did that for you
你们两个好像有什么见不得人的秘密
You both look like you got a dirty little secret
开玩笑的
I'm kidding
看下你们的成果
Let's see how you did
不错啊  小子
Not bad, boys
不错啊
not bad
粉刷平整  富有光泽
A nice even coat, high gloss
毫无起泡
no bubbles
对啊真好看  蟹老板
Yeah, looks great, Mr. Krabs
先走一步
We'll just be going
搞什么鬼  看你们干的好事
Flipping fish parcels, look what you did
别割我们屁股
Please don't cut off our butts
蟹老板  真对不起
Oh, Mr. Krabs, I'm so sorry
干嘛对不起
"Sorry?"
你们给我的小摆设都除尘了
You dusted all my knickknacks
你们可真好啊
That was really nice
搞什么鬼
Great Barrier Reef
这啥东西
What's this?
不能怪我们
That's not our fault
我不想没屁股啊
I don't want to be buttless
踢脚线的漆多半是它自个刷上去的吧
And I suppose the floor molding
just painted itself on its own
这才叫好手艺
That's what I call craftsmanship
老天爷啊
Criminy jim jam
你弄到了我的前
You messed up my dollar
面的娃娃架
rama
娃娃架上面的娃娃原先排得特整齐的
All the dolls in this
dollarama were perfectly aligned
妈妈
Mama
你们居然还以为我注意不到
And you boys thought I wouldn't notice
不过倒也没造成什么损失
Oh, well, I guess no harm done
你们几个可以走了
All right, boys, you're free to go
真奇怪
That's funny
我不记得有这么一大叠画
I don't remember a stack of paintings
叠在我放第一块钱的墙上
jutting from the wall where me first dollar used to be
其实我根本就不记得有这么一幅画
In fact, I don't remember this painting at all
这幅也不记得
Or this one
嗨  蟹老板
Hi, Mr. Krabs
海绵宝宝  你在搞什么
SpongeBob, what are you doing?
就是那个  到处闲晃
You know, just hanging around
挂 着
烂
Boo
站地上来  小子
Get down onto the floor, boy
现在硬要当傻子也没办法
All right, now you're just being silly
不要不要不要
No, no, no
蟹老板  不要啊
Mr. Krabs, no
别看
Don't look
那是骗人的
It's a trick
你们把我第一块钱沾得都是油漆吗
Did you two get paint all over me first dollar?
对不起  蟹老板
We're so sorry, Mr. Krabs
然后你们就用蜡笔在上面乱画吗
And then did you draw on it with crayon?
我以为  人家可能会买账
I thought, you know, maybe he'd buy it
好了  小子
All right, boys
知道我得干什么了吗
You know what I've got to do now?
你是说我们屁股吗
You mean, our butts?
我能最后再用一遍屁股吗
Can I use mine one last time?
可以了  完好如初
There we go, good as new
可
But
对  我骗你们了
Yeah, I lied
这种油漆其实碰到口水就能脱落
This paint actually comes off with saliva
我懂了  蟹老板
I get it, Mr. Krabs
你骗我们这种油漆是永久性的
You told us the paint was permanent
这样我跟派大星就会更加小心
so me and Patrick would be more careful
不让油漆沾到别的东西
and not get paint on anything
错  我只是喜欢整你们
Nah, I just like to mess with you
姜还是老的辣
The old man's still got it
该死
Crud
话得用正常说的  不能到处乱喷
I really got to learn to say it, not spray it
蟹堡王培训视频
分镜总监
分镜
翻译    1440kHz
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
此处点餐
菜单
蟹堡王
入口
欢迎你的加入
Welcome aboard
如果你正在观看本视频
If you're watching this video
那就让我第一个对你说
then let me be the first to say
恭喜你
你已经被蟹堡王餐厅录用了
You've recently been hired
by The Krusty Krab Restaurant
今天是你正式培训的第一天
and this is your first official day of training
我现在可以做蟹黄堡了吗
Can I make a Krabby Patty now?
不行  你还得学不少东西
Oh, no, you've got a lot to learn
才可以去做蟹黄堡
before you're ready to make a Krabby Patty
正如图表所示
As you can see by this graph
[ graph（图表）与 giraffe（长颈鹿）谐音 ]
图表
Graph
录用你的
You are now employed
是全裤头村最成功的餐厅之一
by one of the most successful restaurants
in Bikini Bottom
蟹堡王
但是这并非是一夜之内做到的
But it didn't get that way overnight
因为六点钟就关店了
because the store closes at 6:00
蟹堡王之所以能成功
No, story of The Krusty Krab
关键就在于店长勤奋刻苦  坚毅不拔
is a story of one man's hard work, perseverance
志向远大  矢志不渝
vision, determination
挥洒汗水
and sweat
汗水最关键
But mostly his sweat
白手起家
你可能会想  尤金蟹老板
You may think Mr. Eugene H. Krabs
蟹堡王公司的所有者及创办者
owner and founder of Krusty Krab Inc.
汽水
至今一直都是金融鬼才
has always been the financial wizard he is today
你想得对
And you're right
战后
After the war
蟹老板深陷无尽的抑郁  与世隔绝
Krabs stayed secluded in a deep depression
that seemed endless
但后来他大幅转运
But then his luck changed
收购了一家破产的养老院
when he acquired a bankrupt retirement home
作了几处细微的改变之后
and with a few minor alterations
蟹堡王诞生了
The Krusty Krab was born
蟹堡亡
蟹堡王
听上去好像有很多
Sounds like a lot of
废话
Hoopla
听上去好像有很多
Sounds like a lot
废话
Hoopla
听上去好像有
Sounds like a
废话
Hoopla
听上去好像要讲很多废话
Sounds like a lot of hoopla
才能移交一个小蟹黄堡的所有权对吧
to make over a little Krabby Patty, right?
错
Wrong
今天的蟹堡王
此处点餐
藤壶漂白液
垃圾
严禁续杯
菜单
为跟上现在顾客的日益提高的要求
To keep up with today's demanding customers
我们不惜一切代价
no expense has been spared
采购一切最新快餐科技成就
to acquire all the latest achievements
in fast-food technology
这个是增强型肉饼控制装置
This here is an advanced patty-control mechanism
这边是我们的自动金钱处理系统
Here you see our automated money-handling system
不准摸
Don't touch
这些是高质量饮料温度调控设备
These are high-quality beverage temperature devices
进口的
Imported
这个是液体转移机的原型机
This here's a prototype liquid transfer machine
最重要的是
And most importantly
蟹堡王番茄酱
你可以拿到最先进的散装调味品单位
you get your state-of-the-art
condiment-dispersal units
你要不就买东西
Now are you going to buy something
要不就光站这然后付占地费
or just stand there 'cause there's a standing fee
这些现代化设备似乎把你看晕了吧
All of this modernization
seems a little overwhelming doesn't it?
幸好
Well, luckily for you
蟹老板十分害怕机器人统治
Mr. Krabs' fear of robot overlords
便时刻维持着科技的平衡
keeps the balance of technology in check
不过如果说现代化是蟹堡王的心脏
But if modernization is the heart of The Krusty Krab
那么员工就是肝和胆
then employees are the liver and gallbladder
来看看你有没有相应的素质
Let's see if you've got what it takes
沉着  自信
poised, confident
笑容仿佛在说
and a smile that says
世界你好  我能为你点餐吗
"Hello, world, may I take your order?"
你能成为一个好员工  海绵宝宝先生
You've got the makings
of a good employee, Mr. SquarePants
不过对每个好员工
But for every good employee
总会有个不成器的
there's one who is not so good
来看看
Let's see
不专心  不耐心
inattentive, impatient
目光呆滞
a glazed look in the eyes
仔细看
Look carefully at the
写着  我真希望自己不在这的胸牌
"I Really Wish I Weren't Here Right Now" button
这种员工都有一个外号
There's a name for employees like this
我们都叫他  章鱼哥
but we'll call him Squidward
我这回会有加班费了吧  对吧蟹老板
I'm getting paid overtime for this, right, Mr. Krabs?
对不起  听不见
Sorry, can't hear you
培训
是不是说我现在要去做蟹黄堡了
Does this mean I get to make a Krabby Patty now?
不对  你要做蟹黄堡的话
No, you can't make a Krabby Patty
得要先理解一个字
without understanding the phrase
屎
"POOP"?
你一旦理解了屎的含义
Once you understand POOP
就能理解你在蟹堡王的地位了
you'll understand your place at The Krusty Krab
可是屎是什么意思呢
But what does POOP mean?
其实是一段精心编写的代码
It's actually a carefully organized code
仔细看
Watch closely
大家
都点
我们的
蟹黄堡
屎
POOP
看来海绵宝宝先生理解了屎的含义
Looks like Mr. SquarePants understands POOP
来了一位典型的客人
Here's a typical customer
不知道他要点什么
I wonder what he wants
但只要记住屎字  即可迎刃而解
Well, if we just remember POOP, we can figure it out
我想要点
I'd like to order
你觉得他要点
Do you think he's going to order
A  沙发
B  昂贵的发型
C  蟹黄堡
一份蟹黄堡
One patty, please
屎啊  你从来没让我们失望过
POOP, you never let us down
既然你理解了屎的含义
Now that you understand POOP
想必你觉得自己准备好去做蟹黄堡了
I bet you think you're ready to make a Krabby Patty
蟹黄堡
Krabby Patty
别着急  勤奋的小子
Not so fast, Eager McBeaver
我们还没谈到
We haven't even talked about
个人卫生
蟹堡王的每一名员工
Every employee of The Krusty Krab
请洗鳍
必须执行一套严格的个人卫生准则
must comply with a strict set
of personal hygiene guidelines
海绵宝宝先生
Okay, Mr. SquarePants
要做好上班准备了没
are you ready to prepare for your shift?
好员工总是把自己的手擦得干干净净
A good employee always scrubs his hands thoroughly
一定要把指甲里面洗干净
Be sure to get under those fingernails
也别忘了关节
And don't forget about the knuckles
要确保手心一尘不染
And make sure those palms are squeaky clean
好了  看看洗好的手
All right, let's see those hands
深入细致
Now, that's thorough
确保了你的脚擦得锃亮
After making sure your feet are polished
脸上没有疤痕和疖子
your face is clear of any blemishes or boils
头发干净整洁
and your hair is neat and tidy
你准备好要开启全新一天了
you are ready to start the day
现在来看看章鱼哥是怎么准备上班的
Now let's see how Squidward prepares for his shift
记住  员工都不可以成为章鱼哥
Remember, no employee wants to be a Squidward
既然你干净又卫生了
Now that you're clean and hygienic
想必你觉得自己准备好去做蟹黄堡了
I'll bet you think you're ready to make that Krabby Patty
我准备好了
I'm ready
别急
Whoa, there
我们还有好几个话题要先讲
We still have a few more topics to cover first
你的工作环境
保持工作环境干净整洁特别重要
It's important to keep your area tidy
and free of droppings
但工作环境整洁只是工作的一部分
But a clean workstation is only part of the job
要把脑中的想象化为现实
To make the vision in your head a reality
需要物质的支持
you'll need supplies
好员工总是
and a good employee always
把他的物质支持安排得井井有条
keeps his supplies well-organized
非常好  海绵宝宝先生
Very nice, Mr. SquarePants
物质各得其所
not a pickle out of place
来看看章鱼哥是怎么打理工作环境的
Now let's see how Squidward keeps his workstation
请勿打扰
放心  章鱼哥
Don't worry, Squidward
海绵宝宝先生可以顶替你
Mr. SquarePants can cover for you
既然你的工作环境正常运作了
Now that your workstation is up and running
可能你觉得
perhaps you think
你准备好去做举世闻名的蟹黄堡了
you're ready to make the world-famous Krabby Patty
别急
Calm down
还有好多的时间
There's plenty of time left
我们还得确保你准备好
We have to make sure you're ready
工作的精神方面
for the psychological aspect of the job
与老板谈话
蟹老板  我能加工资吗
Mr. Krabs, can I have a raise?
不能
No
做得好  海绵宝宝先生
Good job, Mr. SquarePants
我现在可以做蟹黄堡了吗
Can I make a Krabby Patty now?
现在我们从幕后走到前线
And now we move
from behind the scenes to the front lines
在此考察工作中最重要的方面
where we'll examine
the most important aspect of the industry
顾客
the customer
或者照我们的说法是  蟹堡客
Or, as we like to say, the "Krustomer"
谁说的话
Who said that?
你是鬼吗
Are you a ghost?
正如动物体内极其珍贵的血液一般
Like precious, precious blood in an animal
顾客让蟹堡王生机勃勃
customers are what keeps The Krusty Krab
strong and alive
章鱼哥  你天花板在跟我说话
Squidward, your ceiling is talking to me
你是要来点餐的
Are you going to order something
还是要来跟天花板交朋友的
or just make friends with the paneling?
我要点
I'll have an uh
干嘛
What's that?
派大星  别在这里发癫
Patrick, go be stupid somewhere else
章鱼哥  记住蟹老板说的话
Squidward, remember what Mr. Krabs says
金钱永远是对的
天花板说得对  章鱼哥
The ceiling is right, Squidward
你就不是个什么好员工
you're not a very good employee
那行
Fine
我可以给你点餐吗
May I please take your order?
我要点
I'll have, uh
我们等会再来看这两个
We'll check in with these two later
现在  我们重点要来讨论
Right now, it's important that we discuss an
紧急情况
正如亚特兰蒂斯失落的黄金
Like the lost gold of Atlantis
很多人把蟹黄堡当作财宝看待
many consider their Krabby Patty to be a treasure
至于每样财宝
And as with every treasure
都会有小偷来偷盗
there's a thief ready to steal it
所以你要负责警惕
So it's up to you to be the watchful eyes of
这是什么
What's this?
是蟹老板的商业竞争对手  痞老板
It's Mr. Krabs' business rival, Plankton
吃灰去吧  老螃蟹
Eat my microscopic dust, Krabs
你的秘密配方终于是我的了
Your secret formula is finally mine
他在偷秘方
He's stealing the formula
你要怎么办  海绵宝宝先生
What are you going to do, Mr. SquarePants?
你永远也抓不到我的  老螃蟹
You'll never catch me, Krabs
我已经换到最大超速档了
not when I shift into maximum overdrive
早知道就装涡轮增压器了
I knew I should've gotten the turbo
听好了  老螃蟹
Hear me, Krabs
你要想从我这拿走这个蟹黄堡
You'll take this Krabby Patty from me
至少也要先让我死透了再
when you pry it from my cold, dead
到这  又一个紧急危机解除了
And so another emergency is avoided
多亏有海绵宝宝先生
thanks to Mr. SquarePants
我们再来看看章鱼哥
Let's check in on Squidward again
章鱼哥
Squidward
要记住
Just remember
屎
派大星  我给你个建议
Patrick, if I could make a suggestion
要不你点个蟹黄堡吧
why don't you just order a Krabby Patty?
好办法  章鱼哥
Great idea, Squidward
一份蟹黄堡
One Krabby Patty, please
堂食还是外带
Is that for here or to go?
别泄气  章鱼哥
Hang in there, Squidward
这都是分内之事
it's all part of the job
培训指南
既然培训的基础知识都学完了
Now that we've covered all the basics of your training
那么该到了你迫切等待的时刻了
it's time for the moment you've been waiting for
制作蟹黄堡
Preparing the Krabby Patty
每个伟大王朝的中央都有耀眼的王冠
At the center of every great dynasty is the crown jewel
蟹黄堡  蟹堡王独家
保持着王朝的兴旺与发达
which keeps it alive and thriving
对于蟹堡王  这个王冠就是蟹黄堡
For The Krusty Krab, this is the Krabby Patty
而现在的你  这份工作里的小小员工
And now you, the humble employee off the street
让这份生意得以维持的必备人力资源
the all-too-necessary human resource
that keeps this business afloat
将会学到一份神圣又黑暗的秘诀
will learn the sacred and dark secrets
指引你亲手制作蟹黄堡
of how to prepare, with your very own hands
那奢华的  那让你嘴唇湿润
The sumptuous, lip-moistening
背脊刺痛  心脏停跳的兴奋中枢
spine-tingling, heart-stopping pleasure center
正是蟹黄堡
that is a Krabby Patty
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
你确定吗
Are you sure?
那好  秘密配方就是
Okay, the secret formula